Mr. Lu,
there's a bit of a traffic jam today.
The driver is stuck on the overpass.
I'm driving Mr. Liu's car in the underground parking lot.
Please wait for me a moment.
Do you know Zhou Jian from the Merchandise Department?
I know him,
but not very well.
Does he have a girlfriend?
Because we're not very close,
I'm not sure about this.
I saw you talking to him in the hallway that day.
Did he do something wrong?
I'll notify HR to terminate his employment tomorrow.
Ah.
No need.
He's quite good.
You go get the car first.
Okay.
I know.
By the way,
don't tell Zhou Jian who I am.
Mr. Lu,
I know.
It's raining heavily.
Hard to get a car off the roadside.
Your department is off work.
Why are you still here?
I just finished the files in hand.
You are so hard-working.
I have to.
If only I could be department manager.
After all, I'm not like you.
You have a good family background,
which is different from me.
How do you know my family background is good?
You are an intern.
I guess your half-year salary
plus overtime pay can't afford this dress.
You can't afford it.
I don't need it.
I borrowed it from you.
Return it to me tomorrow.
Oh,
don't wear such expensive clothes to work again.
If that crazy woman sees you,
it could be dangerous.
Good evening, everyone.
Let's start tonight's Golden Thread
honorary moment with the warmest applause.
The annual promotion commendation banquet
now officially begins.
Why is the protagonist of the celebration
drinking alone here?
I'm not the star here.
Fu Xin is.
Someone like me, who can only afford
a cheap suit with overtime pay,
is just a background.
Who's Fu Xin?
I've never seen his name in the financial reports.
It's normal that you don't know him.
I'm his colleague,
but I've barely seen him.
He's the royalty of the Group.
Mr. Liu wants to use him as a bridge.
After all, the orders from his uncle
are enough to sustain our department for years.
Let's welcome Ms. Lu Qianqian
to read this list of honor for us.
Just say it.
President Lu, it's your turn to present the award to Mr. Fu.
Are you Lu Qianqian, the daughter of the chairman?
Yes.
Are you the woman who
who poured wine on someone for wearing the same dress,
and stuffed her in the trunk?
The crazy woman?
Uh...
Who?
What are you doing?
Hardworking people should be rewarded.
Your overtime pay will turn into dividends.
Your suit will be embroidered with gold thread.
Because from now on,
I'm
your
backing.
But after that party,
everything went out of control
and could not be salvaged.
Drink!
Put me down.
I can still drink.
Drink, drink, drink.
Drink them to death, you bastards.
You can't beat me.
Don't go.
You're clearly interested in me.
Aren't you?
Qianqian,
you're drunk.
Go to bed early.
Qianqian,
thank you for inviting me to the party.
But I really should go back.
Go back?
Go back to Su Muchen?
Zhou Jian,
I like you.
I know you like me too.
When you deleted the surveillance for me,
you were doomed to fall for me.
Divorce Su Muchen.
I can give you more than she can.
I'm sorry.
Why do you need to apologize to me?
You don't need to apologize to me.
I'm sorry.
I took advantage of your feelings for me
to get to where I am today.
I like you too.
But we can't be together.
I'm already married to Su Muchen.
I love her.
You can get a divorce.
You can love me even if you love her.
Come back!
Zhou Jian, come back!
Why don't you choose me?
Come back!
Did I let you go?
I'm with you.
When you come back,
share more love with me.
Lu Qianqian didn't know, did she?
She drank a lot that day.
Mr. Wu,
make an appointment with Su Muchen for me.
Don't let Zhou Jian know.
OK.
I saw the hospital test report when I was 15.
Lu Qianqian
is not your biological daughter.
She has no blood relation with me.
The baby can be anyone's,
but not yours.
Mom,
I'm begging you.
Please, this is the last time I'm asking.
Just let me do this.
Because you're my son,
I've always been lenient with you.
But this time,
I can't.
Ms. An,
over the years,
thank you for taking care of my husband.
The apartment Zhou Jian rented,
which building is it in?
This...
Ms. An,
what do you mean?
I don't understand.
You can't even find
your own home with Zhou Jian.
But my Golden Thread Building
can be a landmark
no matter where you are in the city.
Just say it.
I know everything about
Zhou Jian and Lu Qianqian.
The child of our Lu family
can't be the mistress.
So?
So,
you have two choices.
Either take the money and leave the city,
or
wait for me to choose your tombstone.
I won't divorce Zhou Jian.
Lu Qianqian's baby
is definitely not his.
I can give you everything you want,
but
you can't give me a home.
Muchen.
Su Muchen.
I've told you over and over again
many times.
that there are some things you can't handle.
You can't handle them.
Why don't you listen?
Muchen, where are you? Answer the phone.
Do you know how much trouble you've caused?
So you know everything.
I know.
Although her death was an accident,
it was because Anne pushed her to the edge
that she became mentally unstable
and got hit by a car.
I've been living like a dog
in the Lu family for years,
just for one purpose,
which is to pull down the woman
sitting on the throne of power and prestige, just like you.
But do you know that my sister was pregnant with your child
before she was hit and died?
It seems you don't know.
It was Annie who covered up the truth with lies.
But you chose to remain silent, knowing the truth,
becoming an accomplice to her lies,
and told a lie that is
harder to be found out.
You're really a lady.
Even in such a big event,
you still dress up so beautifully.
Are you Su Muchen's sister?